ixibo.com 2013-03-24

# Privacy Policy | ixibo

Your privacy is of utmost importance to us here at this blog Rest assured that any information you provide will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

This policy may be updated or changed anytime and we encourage you to review it whenever you visit the site to make sure you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

## Collection and Use of Information

We collect personally identifiable information such as names and email addresses only when voluntarily submitted. These information are used merely to fulfill a specific request, for example, to post a comment on our blog, to create an account in our Forum, or to subscribe to our mailing list. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further communications.

## Distribution of Information

We never use or share any of those information in ways unrelated to the ones described above. We do not send spam and we do not sell your information to any company for marketing purposes. We may, however, share information with government agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place.

## Cookies and Tracking Technology

Our site may place a small file, called a cookie, on your hard drive to provide you with a better website. A cookie does not, in any way, give us access to your computer or to any personally identifiable information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. It only helps us analyze web traffic or lets web applications respond to you as an individual.

Our authorized third-party advertisers in the course of serving ads to you, may also place cookies on your browser or use tracking technology to collect information. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser’s settings section.

Google, one of our third-party advertisers, may add a cookie to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. You can choose to opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

## Links to other Websites

Our site may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you use these links to leave our site, we do not anymore have control over that website. Such sites are not governed by this privacy statement and we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information you provide to those sites. Exercise caution and read the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Privacy Contact Information

Should you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy, please contact us by email directly at **webmaster @ ixibo.com.**
